## LIAM KOKAB

E-mail: Liam@Kokab.no
Website: www.Kokab.no
Mobile Phone: +47 93018799
Date of birth: 07.07.1989



## **Profile**

I have programmed since 2012, mostly in Java. Programming is my greatest passion. Much of my spare time is used to accumulate more programming skills by learning new programming languages, keeping updated with the field and engaged in exciting projects. When working with projects I am focused and precise, I will never give up before finding a solution.

## **Technology**

Java, C#, C++, Haskell, MathLab Html, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL

Git, Eclipse, IntelliJ, VS Code, MS Visual Studio

**Education** 

01.2012 - 12.2018 **University of Bergen** 

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Technology

(01.2012 – 06.2014 part-time, 08.2016 – 12.2018. full-time.)

01.2009 - 06.2011 Akademiet and Danielsen

Various subjects to qualify for Bachelor's degree

08.2005 - 06.2009 **Åsane VGS (High School)** 

Electrical, Data and Electronics, General Education.

(3 years of Norwegian high school education.)

**Work Experience** 

09.2011 - 04.2015 Skomakeren i Arken AS (Shoemaker shop)

Customer care, key grinding, producing signs and closing the store.

07.2007 - 09.2009 Renseriet Sandnes AS (Dry cleaning shop)

Customer care, dry cleaning, textile treatment and closing the store.

Language

Norwegian Fluent (speaking, reading, writing).

English Fluent (speaking, reading), excellent (writing).

Persian Fluent (speaking), good (reading, writing).

**Voluntary Work** 

08.2012 – d.d. Aktive student forening

Arranging of concerts.

Arrangement of social events for the association.

07.2005 - 06.2008 Save the children Bergen active

As a youth and adult leader.

Organizing and carrying out activities for the children.

create social events for the children.